test_case,label
"My name is Alice Smith and my email is alice@company.org.","My name is <PERSON> and my email is <EMAIL_ADDRESS>."
"Please send payment to credit card 4111-1111-1111-1111.","Please send payment to credit card <CREDIT_CARD>."
"The meeting is scheduled for January 15, 2024 at the New York office.","The meeting is scheduled for <DATE_TIME> at the <LOCATION> office."
"Visit our website at https://example.com for more information.","Visit our website at <URL> for more information."
"My IP address is 192.168.1.100 and phone is 555-987-6543.","My IP address is <IP_ADDRESS> and phone is <PHONE_NUMBER>."
"Robert Johnson lives at 123 Main Street, Los Angeles.","<PERSON> lives at 123 Main Street, <LOCATION>."
"Send the report to manager@business.net by Friday.","Send the report to <EMAIL_ADDRESS> by <DATE_TIME>."
"Customer ID: 12345, Contact: Mary Williams at 555-111-2222.","Customer ID: 12345, Contact: <PERSON> at <PHONE_NUMBER>."
"Dr. Michael Brown can be reached at michael.brown@hospital.org.","Dr. <PERSON> can be reached at <EMAIL_ADDRESS>."
"The invoice should be sent to accounts@example.com.","The invoice should be sent to <EMAIL_ADDRESS>."
"James Wilson called from 555-333-4444 regarding the order.","<PERSON> called from <PHONE_NUMBER> regarding the order."
"Please verify SSN ending in 6789 for David Lee.","Please verify SSN ending in 6789 for <PERSON>."
"Contact support at help@service.io or 1-800-555-0199.","Contact support at <EMAIL_ADDRESS> or <PHONE_NUMBER>."
"Sarah Davis submitted the application on March 20, 2024.","<PERSON> submitted the application on <DATE_TIME>."
